

Details

Singaporean

+65 88777708

rsprincess2407@gmail.com

Links

https://kittylegacy.gitHub.io/
rosweb/

https://gitHub.com/kittylegacy

https://linkedin.com/in/
rosamund-teng-52597b22b/

Skills

React

Three.JS

Vue JS

HTML5 Canvas

Figma

Blender 3D

Javascript

C#

.NET Framework

PostgresSQL

SQL Scripting

Postman

HTML / CSS

Java

ProCreate

High attention to details

Collaboration & Teamwork

Rosamund Teng

Profile

I am an Ambivert. I strive to do what I call my best in everything I do. I have good working experience. In every job that I have held, I have never let my employer nor my teammates and colleagues down. Its all due to my progressive nature, willingness to learn and be a team player kind of character that I always cultivate in all aspects of my work.

Although it may seemed that I have only experience working in BackEnd, but during my free time I love designing. Currently I'm self picking up Three.JS and Blender 3D to revamp my Portfolio into a 3D responsive web. PS: Still working on it not yet published.

Employment History

Software Engineer Analyst (BACKEND Co.Lead) Lexly Health, Singapore

April 2022 - October 2022

- Fix and develop Backend API using C# .net framework
- Convert company DB sequential ID to GUID
- Refactoring of Backend Api
- Guide new interns
- BackEnd Documenting

Junior Fullstack Devloper Trainee Generation, Singapore

January 2022 - April 2022

UI/UX designning with Figma

Implemented a MVP web application with the following

lavers:

Frontend: HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Spring Boot Backend: REST API with Java

Persistence: MySQL Database.

Education

Temasek Polytechnic (JR. FullStack Developer)

JANUARY 2022 - MARCH 2022

WPLN, British Council (WPLN) SEPTEMBER 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Pava Lebar Methodist Girls School (N lvls)

JANUARY 2004 - DECEMBER 2008

Rosyth Primary School (PSLE)

JANUARY 1998 - DECEMBER 2003